There is a woman there - you put on red, fat.
This is an attack - bedwetting.
Such a young woman. Please, come; it is an attack.
You are fat.
God loves you.
It is an attack; this is not how you were born.
Non-stop.
But it is okay; Jesus loves you.
Prophecy Confirmation
This is the woman I said is bedwetting.
It is an attack.
My name is Ramat Mercy Emeka Mba.
The man of God prophesied to me over the issue of my bedwetting,
and this problem has been lingering in my heart.
I don't know who to cry to or who to talk to.
I cry every night in my room.
You only cry in the night?
I cry in the day; cry in the night.
You are just saying it now.
Yes, Man of God.
What you first said is that you cry in the night.
What of the day?
I will cry in the room; I will not come out to cry, Man of God,
and it has been disturbing me.
I don't know who to cry to.
Okay, it's alright. Don't worry.
- So, you know Jesus?
- Yes.
- There is a solution, okay?
- Thank you.
- Where is your husband?
- He is here.
Come here!
Prophecy Time
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come.
You don't want to be proud of your wife because she is a bedwetter?
No, I'm proud of her.
When you saw your wife coming out, why did you not run out?
Go and carry your wife.
Nobody will help you. Carry her!
Prophecy Time
Look, you have an addiction and poverty is fighting you.
It is true, Man of God.
Poverty is fighting you.
Thank You, Jesus, I'm healed!
See your wife now!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Ramat Mercy Emeka Mba.
This is my husband - my lovely husband.
Mrs Ramat Mercy Emeka Mby & Husband
Delivered From Bedwetting Through Prophecy
The man of God prophesied that there is a woman here, fat.
That she should come out. She has the spirit of bedwetting.
That it is an attack; she should come out.
I knew it was my case and I run out.
I said, "I'm here. It is true, Man of God".
The prophecy is true - thousand percent true.
I thank God for that prophecy. If not, I don't know where I would be now
because it is a very serious thing for you to see a woman, mother, to bedwet.
A very serious story.
Being a mother bedwetting - look at my children by my side.
I would be in my room; I would be with my husband.
When that thing happened, I would be crying, just as I was saying.
I would be crying in the night, "What is happening to me?"
I have children that are supposed to bedwet.
I would then carry them and say, "Don't do this".
As an adult, am I to be doing this?
It was a very serious story.
This bedwetting started when I got married.
It is more than ten years now - ten good years.
When this happened in the night, I would take the mattress outside in the morning.
My workers would say, "Ah, is it yours or from your house?"
I would not even know what to say; I would be too ashamed to tell them this or that
because it was a very shameful thing.
I didn't know what to do. I would say, "Yes, it was my kids".
I had to lie.
I would go inside and start crying again.
My husband would say, "Why are you crying? Leave it. God will do it.
You know the God we are worshipping.
We are members; we will be able to have our healing.
At the right time of God, you will be healed".
He always supported me.
He always stood by me - seriously, what would I have done?
I never used to go out; there would be occasions where they said, "Can we go?"
I would say, "No, I can't".
Because if I went or travelled, this might disgrace me.
I would be ashamed so I wouldn't go.
Even one day, I went to my uncle's wedding and it happened again.
I said, "Ha. What is happening to me?"
So I kept on crying; crying was the only solution.
He would say, "Don't cry".
It really affected my life.
I used to have a dream where I would see a man climbing on top of me - giant.
I said, "Who are you? You are not my husband!"
I would be pushing him.
He would be strangling me by the neck and say, "Lie down".
I would lie down and say, "Who is this?"
At the end, I would wake up from that dream - bedwetting again.
Immediately Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me and touched me,
I felt something heavy removed from my heart.
I am fat - you can see that I'm fat - and I feel light.
Formerly, I would be like a stone.
I used to say, "What kind of heaviness is this? Am I the only fat person in this world?
Am I the only one that is fat?"
Immediately after that touch, the heaviness was removed from my heart.
I was light - light till now.
Mrs Ramat Mercy Emeka Mby & Husband
Delivered From Bedwetting Through Prophecy
Ever since then, my brothers and sisters, I'm sleeping now like a baby.
If I drink water now, I can take four bottles of water.
I even used to test; I drank a lot of water and then go to sleep.
When I sleep - no more!
My people, no more! Help me to thank God!
I am no more bedwetting.
People that used to see me bedwetting, "This fat woman..." - I'm no more bedwetting!
I'm like a new-born baby now.
I thank God for what Jesus has done for me.
I dreamt the day before yesterday.
I saw a giant man - black - and a white man.
The white one was pursuing the other one.
Then I took a knife and said, "You have come again" and then stabbed the black one.
Then I woke up and I was okay.
I'm delivered.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So that is to confirm that that evil spirit, the demon responsible for that bedwetting
was cast out through the prayer and the dream was just a spiritual confirmation
of what Jesus Christ had done.
It is a wonderful thing. I'm delivered.
It was not an easy thing.
I'm delivered; I'm saved.
I thank our daddy in the Lord, Prophet T.B. Joshua, for seeing me out of my big problem.
Big one for an adult to bedwet!
I thank God for him.
May God give him a long life and prosperity!
Give him more and more wisdom!
Mrs Ramat Mercy Emeka Mby & Husband
Delivered From Bedwetting Through Prophecy
Madam, at the end of the prophecy, the man of God said something concerning your husband.
What did he say about your husband and what can you say concerning that?
You could all see towards the end of it...
When they say, "Let's attack the home so that we cannot see the home progress"...
He prophesied, "Can't you come out for your wife or are you ashamed?"
He came out and said, "No".
He said, "You are addicted to drugs and smoking".
It is perfectly true.
I said, "He, is it only me that God loves in this church?"
I was so happy.
The addiction was severe.
Sometimes we took a car and he would say, "Take. Give me drugs".
Before I would look for money again, he would go and collect it.
We would be fighting.
Even the day before we came here, he almost burnt down the room.
I said, "God, help me. It can't happen like this.
He is a father; I'm a mother. Why all this?"
I thank God that the man of God also delivered him.
For one week now, we are like a new creation.
Help me to thank God! Help me to thank Jesus!
No more drugs, no more any trouble again!
We are still coming back for more testimonies.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Anthony Mba.
I came from Abuja.
This is my lovely wife.
Last week during the course of the service, the man of God gave a prophecy concerning my family.
First, he prophesied about my wife who had this problem of bedwetting.
True, people of God. It has not been easy for us as a family.
You people know how it is when your wife wakes up in the middle of the night crying
that she has bedwetted again.
We tried medical solution, going to hospitals.
They said she has diabetes.
But we knew it was not normal.
As God would have it, last week, the man of God prophesied concerning her.
Since last week till now, my wife is free from the spirit of bedwetting.
Also, in the course of the prophecy, the man of God prophesied about me.
I had this addiction to smoking.
I smoked marihuana and cigarettes.
Since my childhood days, I had been addicted to that.
I had tried on my own to stop but it was not easy.
I thank God for the prophecy of the man of God.
From last week till now, the urge is no longer there again.
I thank God for everything.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Wow. Glory be to God Almighty. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
So it is a double testimony.
Not only was your wife delivered from bedwetting, you too were delivered from that drug addiction.
Brother, could you give us an idea of how serious this addiction was before,
how it really destroyed your life.
I didn't even know myself; I didn't know what just came over me.
I can't even explain it.
All I know is that I was very addicted to these things on a daily basis.
I didn't understand what was happening.
I just thank God that since last week, I have been free.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We give glory to our Lord Jesus Christ for this wonderful testimony
Madam, we also understand that some of your family members are here
to rejoice with you for this testimony.
We would also like to invite some of your family members to come forward
as it is such a huge testimony for what Jesus has done in the life of our mother,
setting her free from ten years of that affliction of bedwetting.
as well as our brother delivered from that drug addiction.
My name is Saadatu Ibrahim. This is my sister.
I came with her from Abuja to testify to what God has done in her life.
It has not been easy but glory be to God, she is delivered.
Thanks be to God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ.
It is wonderful that the family has come to join our sister to share the testimony.
My word of advice to people:
You are all sitting in this arena of liberty.
As He healed me, located me and prophesied to me,
it will be the same for you, in Jesus' name!
If you have a problem in your body, don't say that the doctor can do it.
Doctors can only treat but God heals.
As the man of God has healed me, everyone will be located and healed, in Jesus' name.
That is my advice. And don't hide a problem within you,
become ashamed and not come out.
When I heard it, I ran out because I knew it was my problem.
So if you hear yours, don't say, I'm feeling shy. I won't come out.
I will not do this".
Come out! That devil will be put to shame!
He has been put to shame in my life.
So you will put him to shame in yours.
Thank You, Jesus!
Mrs Ramat Mercy Emeka Mby & Husband
Delivered From Bedwetting Through Prophecy
Glory be to God Almighty! We thank God for this wonderful testimony.
We pray that God will give the grace to this family
to continue to make the Word of God the standard for your lives
and we believe the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 18/11/2018